So hey guys welcome back to another day another
vlog.  So how are you all?  Today's vlog we're
starting a little outside.  That means
I have reached the venue all ready.
Me and Mars were just having dinner.  The match has
started.  Meaning the first match
is over and we are just leaving after having food.
Here the side player just ate food from the launch
and Nihal lost the first match.
Now let's see what's going on.
Mars has been removed.  I just went along to get some
water and this so let's go and see
what happens.  What are the results of the match now?  Let's
go.   The
match is going on.   It's
difficult brother.  It will be tough, right?
But he can defeat it, he has defeated it before also, so it
means he
can defeat it brother, our guy is no less than two, brother,
such support brother, are you watching
Rocket League, on top of that brother, there is a lot of
craze for Rocket League also, it means every
game has some craze or the other which we are
not aware of, but it is,
I am saying, it
seems like
I am saying, every game has a craze
and let's keep
watching that,
they don't do this much.  People don't know
that every game has its craze.  Different place
here most thing is friends audience
is very crazy for e sports.  Like
literally they are very mad.   You
can go here.
I look here every day.  It is going on.  It is
going on.  Were not playing yesterday.
These people were not there.
No,
we have
brought a
Mega F from Kob, he has a
Mega phone in his hand,
yes it is happening, it is happening, it is happening, he has
saved it
[encouraging voice]
and the situation is going on, I don't know what it is, it is
coming now, friend, even if there is a draw,
Nihal will be out, I was
talking, if there is a draw, then he has won, whatever amount he has to pay.
Two matches have to be won.  Ca
n't even draw a draw.
Nice,
what's here is about to finish.
[Music]
Hey guys, look who's here?
Come my Lambu ji, come forward.  Have you come, how did you do it, I will
go to the gym in the evening, what is this
stick, you have bought
this new camera, what do you do with it, not just
yours but the person in front gets
recorded, so
no tension, the person
behind gets recorded as well and there is no problem in editing,
once you learn something, it is very good
but it is better than this, there is pocket four,
yes
buy that, it is better, I used that
here in my London blog, okay, but I
bought that one from someone, from a friend,
where did you get this one, then
this one is already there, I had taken this one to Nepal, I had
bought it for Mount Everest.   Come on
brother, he is
doing gym here also.  Brother has not left this gym.
Hello, brother.
How are you brother?
Hey brother, I got
emotional.   It's
okay brother, I
met Arjun brother, he commented,
I said come to the venue, let's meet, so
he has given me this gift and has
brought these chocolates brother, thank you friend,
thank you brother,
yes take it, take it, crazy brother,
you made it with your own
hands
brother, how much time did it take
me, it took me two days
brother, the 30 million one is also less than yours brother, see
what came next [laughs],
20 came,
20 is
coming, 100 million.
Brother, I will do it too.  wait.  So guys, we have done
some shopping.  The bulls are
stuffed.
So I had said I would take it, but it got a little late but I took it.
What?  Hey, move aside, let me do it too.
Why are you blowing your chest?  Checkw.
How long will your chest take?  Are?
Look, I saw $1 million.  [laughter]
Hey brother, look at this.  Oh mother, I swear.
Hey, the $20 that I got was
for the face, I got more on the apps.
Yes, there is more on the app.  I gave you $20 for your looks.   This is
free, isn't it?
No, this one is a $10 one.  I spent 20.   It's
free.  I know you can't spend money.
This is free.  I know from the first day that it is
free.  Listen, the elders also come.
Yes.
Cards here and there.
He is free.
₹15
Buy Two Get One Free.  You can give me the free one.
Buy two get one free.  What?
Yes.  If you get two done, one is free.
Come on lady, apply it.  You didn't come today with the luck, so
how much did you get,
how much did you get, how much did you show, show how much
[laughs]
2.6 million did
not come,
hey let me eat the
Campa, hey,
where is it, it's come, it's written, the
Campa has come, Dekhti ST's, that has also come,
yes, the people have also come, yes,
keep this, I have
not taken it, yours continue for me,
please do it,
brother, will you do it yourself, hey, move aside,
when it comes, tell me, tell me in three seconds,
kid, ca
n't you see, I want
100 million, brother, 100
million, three two,
one
zero, it's
fun,
just 100 million, 100 million will
not come,
100 million,
20 [laughs]
hey, listen, in this form, nothing will come,
I feel like you will say,
what's the matter, you make records everywhere, what do you say, it was
divided,
$30, that record,
no, no, no, friend,
how much was it, 18,
30, hey, show me the 30, it's
30 for both the three people
there also, here also there is 30 of one, hey, I did
n't see less than 30, I just showed this, I did
n't see less than 30, I
just show you this, should I put it, oh
my god
listen, what is that one that is going to be put here, go and put it, that
stick here, that is on the back,
brother sign it, the value will be $100 for 100,
yes go and put it, no, go and
sign it, they will
say which scoundrel is this, the one with 20, he will say did you
steal the purse [laughs]
I will tell you, how is your hair,
your hair doesn't look like a thug's, I look like a thief, no, no,
he doesn't look like a street thief, he is the one who
steals purses,
how much, come on, it is
coming to 100 million,
guess it, guess it is
3.9 million, 39, 39 million,
but he did not give that brother,
he did not give the face made, otherwise it would have come
because he is making it with this only.
Come on, do it.  [Music]
They're coming in at 1 billion and 2.4 billion.
Move.   moved away.  moved away.  moved away.  moved away.  moved away.   Let me
tell you.
1 billion [sound of clearing throat] here it is
from the Alliance.  [laughter]
Now your brother is going to break this record.
See.
That 20 one.
Hey, someone please pause it.
Then you stuck it, right?
Come on, I will show you.   He
stuck two.  And if it came out of this, then
20 and one came out.
[laughs] 10 was out, brother, it was fun.
okay brother.  Make fun of it.  I am not getting any less than you.   I do
n't know why it seems more of it will
come from there.
No, he doesn't know my height, right?   It will take
so much time.  Hey, so much to
write down.  Hey, it is taking time to write the number.
Time taken for digits to print out.
Came.  Oye Oye how many?
700 million.
702 million.  Oh, I thought he would hit the exit.
Aaya aaya aaya aaya aaya aaya
what's the matter Bey yes Bey
what did you say where is yours
what is yours
[laughs]
oy this is even less, I am
not able to match mine [laughs] I don't
know if the public will get it done for 2 million then we will know, get it done, if you do
n't answer then I am leaving, does
anyone know this much less, friend.   I have got the
least amount of money in this.
[laughs]
This water
kake is another one I did.
So much laughter,
I have another one coming.  To check.  702
million came, right?  Now see, if
my piece has come then take a look at it.  I am even more insulted.
He has gone away, right?   The
billion has arrived.
You feed him dinner.
Billion.   If you have
billions then you are feeding me dinner.
He has three billion.   There
is nothing in it.
That photo.  Okay, this Joker has looked from here to do this, okay, hey, it is
not coming, it is finished, his ghee is finished,
Joker, hey,
his ghee is finished, let's buy it
tomorrow, it has come, hey, I
swear to God, it is
fine today, it is less than Joker, it is
more than Joker, so guys, it is almost
10 in the night here, okay, no, not
10, it is 5:15 and look at the day,
you guys, it is already late in the day and brother, whatever has happened today, the
players of PUBG Mobile have fallen ill,
brother, I don't know what has happened, many
people have suddenly fallen ill.  You must have
shown it to people and seen it
on the streams that it was probably over after four matches.
He had closed it.   I don't know what happened to
him.
No update has come yet.  Meaning, his remaining
matches will probably start tomorrow only when he gets well.  Right now
he might have said that it will be done
tomorrow.  Let's see what happens.
But I hope all the players recover well
and play their matches safely.  And the chess
finals are tomorrow and today Magus has
reached the finals.  And
just look, we're all leaving for
dinner right now.  The weather has become so nice that
I feel crazy about you.
So guys, we have just come for dinner.  We have
come to the same place where I had
come with Rega for dinner, sorry lunch.
And I am sitting on the same table and the same chair.
I was sitting on this chair right here
and Aman's update also came.  I have received a
call from my driver.  But
I guess he is coming to give it.  He
told me so.  I will update you when I get it.
Ok?  We are
sitting like this.  Everyone else is there.  We are single
boys here.
Ok.
Brothers, look at the Coke available here and there, I am getting
Coke Zero in the glass class.  He does
n't come to my side.
I haven't seen it except for the can.
He might come there soon.  Shown classic.  So we are having our
meal.  Eating here.  This
brother is eating fish.   The
fish one is on the die.
This doesn't come in our glass.   I don't know.  I don't know.
Brother, I haven't even seen bottles these days.
I have forgotten this.
When is he a man?   I do
n't know in which era.  So guys,
we have just gone out for a little walk.  After this
we are going to some other place a little nearby.  We have
our younger wife with us.  So
now there is a 400 meter walk.  Let's just walk a little and then
leave.  Brother, what a cool breeze is blowing.
Look weather is also light water.  It's outside
because it's raining.  It is just
drizzling lightly.  Meaning I am feeling it.
And the weather is very nice.  And
I'll keep the phone in my pocket.  I will not keep it outside
brother.  I have
heard that it happens a little here.
Come for.  Oh ho ho guys,
look what have you seen, Lambo
and this Lambo brother is BGMI Lambo, the one I
have is a two seater one, by the way two sim,
same colour brother, green colour,
what a thing.  Hey, we will drive it in GT, friend, all this is
here, we have a
lot of it, friend, who drives in GT,
brother, here and here, our brother in cap is
wiping so much, friend, the people outside with him, he
just played the song, thank you friend, thank
you, thank you, I thought you would have a problem,
I was not keeping it, that's okay, you should have
asked me, is the
song good, okay,
listen, Ghulam has come secretly,
or
[laughs]
think you guys should get
[music]
[laughs]
what have you come
wiping.
What are you doing, man?
[laughter]
Hey, look at the water lying around.
This is not jet spray,
sometimes
this jet spray, I don't know
why it is here with you?  Why don't we have it?   gone.
Hey, it is not there even in our hotel.   Let's take it and go.   Will I take it down and
take it?  First
came the address in the washroom.  I thought you had it
installed.   I have
not cleaned the fan in the house till date.   It
also comes out from our AC.  Have I ever done anything to
clean that place? Hello, let me
keep that first, if it gets up, it will
block it.
Hey, hey, it doesn't smell well. It smells
[laughs]
Hey, it is wet. Hey, it will go into the mouth a little. It is
wet, it is heavy.
Okay, when it was kept in front of the fan,
dust was not coming out of it,
brother, you are not able to do it. Wait, it has to be done with hot water. It has not gone out.
Hey, keep it here. When it was in the fan, dust was not
coming out of it,
I am going to do one more thing. Let's add 100 more.
Just look, he is not coming.
Look at his feet, they are so dirty.
Hey, his feet are dirtier than that.
Listen [laughs] are
you talking too much?   He
knows what about your feet [laughs],
stop it, don't do it.   Was a
mechanic.   The
entire fan is working fine.   wait wait wait.
Put it.   Are going.
Now [laughter] wait wait.
Assistant sir, if the fan is not ready then come here.
Assistant sir,
oh sorry, come here first, please get it sorted out with your boss, I have sent the
message, I need it,
boss, do you need any help? [laughs]
with my weapon,
think, I just switched on the fan, nothing happened,
right?
Yes,
what's the matter,
it is drying, my
neck got stuck inside the fan, like this, yes
[screaming sound]
₹00 [laughter] I
saved
from here,
this is worth 2000, Jai Shree, this one that
broke the next day comfort,
nothing, he is lying,
how did the head get stuck in the commode, he is
saying that he slipped, the
second day I am
not exaggerating, the second day
morning I got a message that
I had broken the commode [laughter] then it did
not happen
brother, how does a commode break, it had just
fallen, it
broke like this, how did it fall, friend, it did
not hurt my head, it hit my
hand, oh wow, so guys,
we have just come
back to our hotel, oh, how is the wind blowing,
see, there is a complete storm, there was no wind blowing there,
we were sitting in the balcony, now so much wind has started blowing
What's the matter here?  Come on guys, let's end the vlog here.
See you guys
in the next vlog.  By the way my flight is 16.
So today it is 15.  15 means it has started.
And we are making our comeback.  Tomorrow we are going for a
walk.  So let's go for a walk.  Is
this something that is on your neck?   I like the
lighting like this.  Let's go guys.
Take care.  Good night.  Bye-bye.